put bags
take squash
put squash
take salmon
put salmon
take chicken
put chicken
take can
put can
take squash
take salmon
put it in fridge
put squash
put salmon
close fridge
take squash
open coverage
put squash
close cover
take chicken
open fridge
put chicken
close fridge
take food
put food
take onions
put onions
take crisps
open coverage
put crisps
put food
Take sweet corn
Close cupboard
Open freezer
Pull out drawer
Put sweet corn
Close drawer
Close freezer
Take bag
Fold bag
Take box
Put box
Take knife sharpener
Open drawer
Take knife
Close drawer
Sharpen knife
Continue sharpening knife
Put knife sharpener back
Take kitchen towel
Clean knife
Put towel in bin
Put knife
Open cupboard
Take cutting board
Put cutting board
Open fridge
Pull out drawer
Close fridge
Take onion
Take knife
cut onion
take bin
take top off bin
cut onions in bin
peel onion
put peel onion
put peel in bin
chop onion
slice onion
open cupboard
take bowl
close cupboard
put bowl
Put onion in bin
Transfer onions
Put knife
Take onion
Cut onion
Peel onion
Put peel in bin
Pick up onion
Peel onion
Put peel in bin
Slice onion
dice onion
slice onion
throw onion in bin
clean knife
open cupboards
take bowl
put bowl
close cupboard
transfer onion
Put board
Put bin
Put lid on bin
Open fridge
Take chicken
Close fridge
Put chicken
Open drawer
Get knife
Close drawer
Open chicken
Put chicken on cutting board
Slice chicken
Dice chicken
Cut chicken
Put chicken in bin
Slice chicken
Dice chicken
Wash hands
Get soap
Turn off tap
Dry hands
get sauce pan
put sauce pan
turn on hob
get olive oil
open olive oil
pour olive oil
close olive oil
put olive oil
get kettle
fill kettle
put kettle
turn on kettle
open cupboard
grab measuring cup
close cupboard
get stock
put stock
open cupboard
get almonds
open fridge
get garlic paste
close fridge
get stock cubes
close cupboard
put stock cubes
put garlic paste
put almonds
get stock cubes
open stock cubes
take a stock cube
close stock cubes
put stock cubes
open stock cube
put wrapper in bin
crumble stock cube
open drawer
get spoon
close drawer
open drawer
get bag
close drawer
put onion in bin
open bag
put chicken in food bag
take chicken out of food bag
take chicken
cut chicken
dice chicken
take onions
put onions in sauce pan
put bowl
take chicken
slice chicken
dice chicken
pour kettle into stock
put kettle
stir stock
Turn on tap
Stir stock
Wash hands
Shake pan
Grasp it
Turn off tap
Dry hands
Open drawer
Grab spatcula
Close drawer
Stir
Put plastic on side
Put bag in bin
open drawer
get spoon
get can opener
open can
put can on side
stir onions
open drawer
close drawer
grab spoon
stir onions
continue stirring onions
take chicken
use smasher
put chicken into pan
put chopping board
take ball
put ball
stir fudge
grab garlic paste
put garlic paste
close garlic paste
stir fudge
grab spices
open spice
pour spice
close spice
put spice
grab spice
open spice
pour spice
Close spice
Put spice
Grab spice
Open spice
Pour spice
Close spice
Put spice
Grab spice
Open spice
Pour spice
Close spice
Put spice
Grab pepper
Put pepper
Close pepper
Stir food
Grab olive oil
Open olive oil
Pour olive oil
Close olive oil
Put olive oil
Stir food
Grab garlic paste
Open fridge
Put garlic paste
Close fridge
Stir food
Check food
Grab pans
Grab plate
Open cupboard
Put plate
Put pans
Open cupboard
Put plate
Close cupboard
Grab lids
Grab lunchbox
Open cupboard
Put lunchbox
Put lids
Grab glass
Put glass
Grab cutlery
Open drawer
Put cutlery
close drawer
open fridge
grab squash
close fridge
stir food
open squash
pour squash
put down glass
close squash
open fridge
put squash
close fridge
pickup squash
turn on tap
fill squash
turn off tap
put down glass
stir food
pick up bottle
pour onions
stir food
put onions in pan
continue stirring food
take spice
open spice
pour spice
close spice
take spice
open spice
pour spice
close spice
put spice
serve food
pick up coconut milk
pour coconut milk
spoon coconut milk
put can
pour stock
spoon stock
put measuring cup
stir food
pickup stock
pour granules
close stock
put stock
stir food
continue stirring food
open cupboard
grab lid
put lid on saucepan
turn down hob
put spatula
take spoon
wash spoon
put spoon on side
grab
put stuff
wash can
grab lid
wash lid
put lid in can
turn off tap
put can on side
open lid
close lid
grab can
put can
grab knife
cut knife
open drawer
put counter
close drawer
grab almonds
grab drink
put drink
turn up heat
clean side
put side in bin
turn down heat
pick up glass
put glass
turn down heat
[END SUBTITLE]